

Interface + UX/UI + Product Designer & Front-end Developer

M hello@biancanegron.com

biancanegron.com 646 716 1657

Art, Design and Fashion are worlds I was instantly drawn to by being born and raised in New York City. Immediately I fell in love with all things design. I deciding while attending Queensborough Community College to focus on Design and Technology. I was always fascinated with the World Wide Web and the unlimited possibilities that come with it. After graduation, my goal was to continue learning and researching to always be ahead of the game because design and technology is forever changing. I am passionate about building meaningful experiences. I strongly value thoughtful collaboration with clients and teammates to help shape the projects vision, connect with the target audience, understand and solve problems, and see the design through concept and implementation.



## **EXPERIENCE**

Apr 2016 - Now

Boom Fantasy, Freelance Designer

Redesigning iOS mobile app, user onboarding and created presentations to present to potential partners/investors for mobile startup.

Dec 2014 - Now

Universal Music Group, Senior Digital Designer

Design interfaces for a vast array of recording artists and label groups such as Island Records. Provide direction to team on functionality, user-flow, animations & interactivity.

Jun 2012 - Nov 2014

Latina Magazine, Web Designer & Developer

Redesigned company website and sister site thelatinkitchen.com. Developed on front-end of Drupal CMS. QA tested across all devices and browsers. Created ad units & marketing emails.

Oct 2011 - Dec 2014

Milito Group, Freelance Designer & Front-end Developer

Designed print material & digital products/interfaces. Built websites within Wordpress CMS.

Sept 2007 - Now

Bianca Negron LLC, Freelance Designer & Front End Developer Wireframing, UX/UI Design, Prototyping & Front-End services for clients worldwide.



## **EDUCATION**

**HOBBIES & INTERESTS** 

Associates in Applied Science, New Media Technology Queensborough Community College - Bayside, NY Completed 2012

Photography Typography Traveling Cats

Music (mostly rock and alternative) TV Series (ie: The Walking Dead, G.O.T) Reading Fiction and Sci-Fi Adventure

AREAS OF EXPERTISE



## SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Dreamweaver Javascript/Jquery HTML5 & CSS3 Sass







## UX/UI Design **Branding** Responsive Design Minimalism User Flows Wireframes Cross-browser Testing Prototypes Pixel Perfection Teamwork Front end Development Deadlines